I should mention now that I've been
asked to approve a few things. A UV ad
from the database engineer and now
creating the next project by the
front-end engineer and that's great. I
haven't done dangerously skip
permissions which I I might have done
yolo mode if I were using the sandbox
that we were looking at before. But in
this this case, it's good that I get to
approve these things. Uh as should you
because I want to make sure I know what
kinds of commands are being run,
particularly when we're in this kind of
chaotic uh setup. And it's now a few
minutes later and the the first the
database engineer has completed the SQL
setup. And so the backend engineer has
been kicked off. And you can now see
that that that is happening. There's a
backend engineer. If I do my shift up
and down, you can see that we can flip
between now the team lead, the backend
engineer, and the front-end engineer.
It's interesting that it is a bit more
serial than I was expecting. I guess I
had some sense when I when I put in that
prompt at the beginning that they were
all going to kick off and start working
because you could imagine you could
begin the backend work before the the
database is completely finished. And so
it's it is quite serial and that does
make sense that is a more structured
organized way of doing it that probably
leads to better outcomes a bit less
chaotic and more managed. So, it's
probably a good thing to see that. And I
imagine that by tweaking that initial
prompt, I could have encouraged it to
try and be a little bit more put
everything in parallel, run more
concurrently, but you'd probably get
worse outcomes. And I'm happy to see the
backend engineer is now complete. Uh the
backend engineer is done. Uh 121
passing. All 121 tests are passing. It's
been marked as complete. It's being shut
down again. A bit more serial than I was
expecting. and then spawning the AI
engineer now unblocked. And in some
ways, you could also argue perhaps this
is sensing that that the AI the LLM
engineer and the backend engineer could
have been the same sub agent. Although
perhaps it's good to preserve some
context and keep them as as separate,
but they didn't need to run concurrently
or at least it was perhaps ill advised.
Certainly our our team coordinator felt
it was ill advised to run them
concurrently. And I noticed I'm pleased
to see that it's pointing out that it
needs to be through open router
cerebrass. I'm going to be interested to
see if it ends up using the skill
properly as it should. Uh and I imagine
it will and it will we will be able to
tell from from whether it it knows how
to assign it to Cerebrass. And so this
seems to be happening. Um I can see that
we've got uh now oh now we have more
agents running. Let's take a look. We've
got the team lead, the DevOps engineer,
the front-end engineer, and the LLM
engineer. They are all running. So, for
the first time, we have four sub agents,
not sub agents, four agents running in
our team. It's all happening. There's
just tons going on now. Uh you can see
that uh that lots of um of of different
tool calls happening. Now, it's asking
me now whether it can proceed with
running some some tests. Absolutely. I'm
going to press two chimod commands.
Okay. So, it's wanting to to give um
power to run scripts. This is a clear
case of when I should press one and not
two. I'm happy for it to change the the
ownership of these scripts to change
them so I can execute them. But I want
to approve that every time. And let's
see what's this that one. This is this
is for testing. I'm happy for to press
two for that. So, making good decisions
about whether to to approve only in this
case or always approve is important. We
see these are all running. You can see
how many tool uses have happened already
and how many tokens are coming out of
these. The front end engineer 93,000
tokens. Uh lots going on. Docker build.
I'm happy for it to be able to do that.
Uh I'm pressing two for that. Um that is
the DevOps engineer running that. So you
can see and and uh again that's that's
fine. You can see lots going on. I'm
approving for each of the different
workers and I see stuff is Docker just
just launched. So I wasn't running
Docker uh and it saw that. That was my
mistake. I should have opened Docker. It
just launched Docker uh and uh started
it. Good. Good for it. Amazing. And
that's definitely an example of
something that Opus 4.6 could handle
that models couldn't handle in the past.
That was my mistake. Um and on it goes.
See you in a second. Okay, we're now
done with everything except it's
explaining just the LLM engineer is
done. The front end engineer is done.
We're just waiting for the DevOps
engineer to finish building and then
it's going to pass over to the
integration tester. And I'm I'm
interested I'm a bit concerned that if
the integration tester finds problems,
how is it going to be able to to
delegate back to the the uh the agents
that have completed? So that's going to
be one to watch out for. See how that
coordination works. Okay, everything has
now completed except the integration
tester. And so it is spawning the
integration tester as it says the final
agent. We'll see how it handles any
problems that it has. But that is now
the only other agent running except for
our our our boss, our team lead. There
you go. I just press shift up so I could
see that. Um and uh I remember CtrlT is
how I toggle the task list. There's the
task list. CtrlT toggles the task list
off and on. And shift up and down is how
you flip between the different team
members. Uh good shortcut keys to know.
So uh now it's running the integration
tests. We'll see how this goes. And uh
then we uh yeah, we'll see where it
handles any problems with the
integration tests and then we'll see
whether the thing works. So, it's been
testing for quite a while. I have to say
it's been going for 11 minutes. And I
can see here uh the integration tester
found five API response mismatches
causing a front-end crash. And the the
team lead says, "Good catch. Uh yes, fix
blah blah blah." And it says the
integration tester is now fixing the
response format mismatches. So, I was
hoping it was going to be the original
front-end developer that would fix the
problems. I guess it wants the
integration tester to do the fixing. Uh,
I will let it do its thing. I'm not
going to contradict. We will let it
finish. See where it gets to. See if
that was a good pattern or maybe should
have prompted it differently at the
beginning. Or maybe even I should jump
in now. But for for this one, I would
rather just let it be. Let it complete.
Let's see where it gets. And that is a
wrap. So, it completed all of the tasks.
Uh, it uh found the bug with the five
API responses. A minor note, the CSS
layer overlap. Uh, but nonb blocking. I
guess we'll see that to run the app.
It's got the instructions. Well, we
shouldn't need to do that cuz there
should be Oh, there we go. It says
there's a script. Start Mac. Uh, it's
finished. The teammate shut down
gracefully. The team is cleaned up. The
finally project build is complete. Six
agents, six tasks, all done. The app is
ready to run. So there we've got lots of
stuff. We've got lots of files changed.
Uh fair enough. I think uh it's time for
us to try this out. Okay. I'm going to
start a new terminal window. I am going
to do scripts
slashstart
mac. Oh, that's not good. What have we
got here? Start uh sorry, start
underscore mac. There we go. Okay, here
we go. And it's coming up at localhost
to 8,000, but that didn't seem to run.
There we go. Bam.
Okay, that's pretty cool. This is the
market data watch list on the left. You
can see that it's flashing. We can see
everything going on. We've got an AI
assistant. We've got a portfolio. We've
got 10,000 in cash. Uh let's see now.
What do we do? We can do ticker. Let's
let's try and do some uh some buying.
Let's buy some JP Morgan stock. Why not
to buy? Bam. There we go. JP Morgan has
appeared here. The heat map shows it as
zero. This is amazing. Uh, okay. Now,
why is there we go? It has just changed.
The heat map has changed. That trade and
this is of course all fake market data.
That is a negative and now it's a
positive. Uh, that's nice. Uh, as we go
into the plus, what else should we get
from from here? Let's let's add in uh
some Google stock ticker Google
quantity. And look at that. The cell
just moved across. That's a little bit
of a blip. Let's buy that. Now it comes
in our portfolio heat map right here. Uh
what happens if we click on here? What
does this price chart here give us? I'm
not sure. Uh this is this is the
portfolio P&L showing right here. This
is all pretty cool. It's got the right
color scheme with the the my favorite
colors, but also looking very active.
This is uh with with perhaps a couple of
things that might be improved. Uh it
looks like we're getting some zeros
success working first time, but now we
have to try out the AI assistant. Okay.
So, let's go over to the AI assistant
and say, um, please,
uh, add spy to the watch list.
Let's see what it does. It's thinking
about that. Spy has been added to your
watch list. And there it is on the watch
list. Uh, it doesn't seem to be
changing, though. That's interesting.
Um, okay. Then uh we'll say um please
buy one
share of V.
Uh let's see what that does.
And it just did uh executed purchase of
one share of V at market price. Bam. And
there it is on the heat map. And this
heat map is uh is is obviously like one
where larger boxes represent more more
uh portfolio weight.
um in dollar terms. That's really cool.
There's a lot to take in here. You can
tell I'm slightly frazzled as I try and
absorb all of this. This seems to be a
bit of an error right here that that
this price chart doesn't seem to fill
in. Um but this is all working. It's
able to respond here. The overall
portfolio P&L, this line appears not to
be moving, but it's pretty good. I would
say that that this is um this is an
impressive setup. Yeah, you can see
everything is happening here. The
portfolio price is adjusting. The amount
of cash I've got has come down, of
course. Uh, it's uh it's looking really
excellent. Um, please give me some
trading advice.
See what it says if we do this. Uh, your
portfolio is cash heavy with small
position in Google. Consider
rebalancing. Um, uh, oh, and I just
noticed that the portfolio P&L is it is
changing like this. That's great. uh
please do this for me. Let's see how
that does. Just giving it a uh a request
to do some portfolio rebalancing.
Everything appears to have stopped. It's
thinking that's caused it some
constonnations. There we go. Sold your
two shares of JP Morgan to free cash for
rebalancing. Okay, fair enough. Uh I
don't think that was a great move, but
if if what it wanted to do was to to
bring in more cash into equity, but
there we go. It's working. It's cool.
It's amazing to see this. It definitely
has the live dynamic sense. And most
importantly, it's it's hanging together.
It's it's uh the functionality is there.
It's tested right. A couple of quibbles
like this section here that seems to be
uh a bit a bit unawarks.
How about you? Okay. Well, I've closed
that window down. I'm intrigued to see
that I can bring it back up and it just
continues where it was just as we had
specified. Now, what we could do now is
go in and fix those various bugs. give
it some feedback and fix them. But I
think it's more interesting for us to
give this zeroshot idea another try with
some other workflows. So let's now stop
this server scripts/stop_mac.shell.
It's stopped. Okay, great. And now we're
going to do a git status and see
everything that's in here. There's a lot
of stuff that's been built. Okay, now
I'm going to do a git add dot. That's
putting everything into git uh and uh
and into so it's staged for commit.
Let's do another git status and see what
that looks like. Now, lots of things
have been set up here. Uh and let's just
make sure that there's nothing in here
that looks concerning. It hasn't checked
in uh node modules or anything. No,
everything is correctly get ignored. And
there's a docker ignore and there's
av.ample
but not av file. That all seems great.
Um, okay. Then just double checking.
Good. Then what we're now going to do is
now do a a a git push but to this
branch. We're going to commit and then
push to agent- teams. So get commit
minus m uh agent teams v1
get push origin
agent teams.
And off it has gone. So that has now
been pushed to that branch agent teams.
Excellent. Look at what we can do now.
Thanks to the power of git, we can do
git checkout main. And all of our code
flips back to where we were before. Bam.
Gone. Okay, great. Now on to the